[Phone ringing]
Thanks for
[Privacy beep]
I'm Liv, how can I help?
Hiya, I just wanted to ring in and book an appointment.
Thanks, can you please tell me
if this is for you or someone else?
It's for me, I'm new in the area,
I want to register with the dentist
and then get checked up as well.
Got it, are you looking for
a new patient check-up appointment?
Also, do you have a day or time that suits you best?
Ideally today, if we could do later on today,
that'd be great and yeah,
this would be a new patient check-up.
The first available appointment this afternoon
is at 2.30 or three in the afternoon or 3.30.
Which one works for you?
Can we do three o'clock?
Thanks, may I have your full name
and the best phone number to reach you on please?
Yeah, my name is Tristan Adams
and the best number to reach me on is this one.
[Contact detail privacy beep]
Your new patient check-up appointment
is booked for Wednesday, the 7th of October
at 3pm.
The team has all your details
and looks forward to seeing you then.
Is there anything else I can help with?
No, that would be all. Thank you. Bye-bye.